{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590896439","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590896438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 83406da6-55a9-4c71-a508-83f34a227b6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" fulana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590906089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590906089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 94d59ac5-5f3b-4ad5-977d-7fffa46673e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_k-f-s"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590915941","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590915941"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 94d59ac5-5f3b-4ad5-977d-7fffa46673e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_p-s-f"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590925444","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590925444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 94d59ac5-5f3b-4ad5-977d-7fffa46673e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-n-b"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590936405","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590936405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 94d59ac5-5f3b-4ad5-977d-7fffa46673e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_l-f-o"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590941470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590941470"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 94d59ac5-5f3b-4ad5-977d-7fffa46673e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_p-n-f"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590946620","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590946619"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 94d59ac5-5f3b-4ad5-977d-7fffa46673e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-u-f"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590951694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590951693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 94d59ac5-5f3b-4ad5-977d-7fffa46673e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-z-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590955523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590955523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 94d59ac5-5f3b-4ad5-977d-7fffa46673e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_n-f-b"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590959166","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590959166"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 94d59ac5-5f3b-4ad5-977d-7fffa46673e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-j-e"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590962799","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590962799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 94d59ac5-5f3b-4ad5-977d-7fffa46673e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_y-f-k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590968542","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590968541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 94d59ac5-5f3b-4ad5-977d-7fffa46673e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_f_y-f-k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590977511","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590977510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 94d59ac5-5f3b-4ad5-977d-7fffa46673e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_f_y-f-k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590990556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590990556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4820243e-3aa9-4f19-aa18-d1db90cd89c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_w-ch-f"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590993435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590993435"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4820243e-3aa9-4f19-aa18-d1db90cd89c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-s-d"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590997300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590997300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4820243e-3aa9-4f19-aa18-d1db90cd89c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_l-f-w"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591002998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591002998"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4820243e-3aa9-4f19-aa18-d1db90cd89c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_k-f-l"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591006647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591006647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4820243e-3aa9-4f19-aa18-d1db90cd89c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-l-ch"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591010025","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591010024"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4820243e-3aa9-4f19-aa18-d1db90cd89c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_r-f-l"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591013589","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591013589"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4820243e-3aa9-4f19-aa18-d1db90cd89c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_v-z-f"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591017694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591017693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4820243e-3aa9-4f19-aa18-d1db90cd89c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_s-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591021113","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591021113"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4820243e-3aa9-4f19-aa18-d1db90cd89c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_b-f-e"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591030599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591030599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4820243e-3aa9-4f19-aa18-d1db90cd89c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-ch-g"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591036340","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591036339"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4820243e-3aa9-4f19-aa18-d1db90cd89c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-ch-g"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591046108","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591046107"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 30c3cffb-b148-424b-98b2-33ca72a987c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591046341","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591046340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 30c3cffb-b148-424b-98b2-33ca72a987c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591047316","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591047315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 30c3cffb-b148-424b-98b2-33ca72a987c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591048608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591048608"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 30c3cffb-b148-424b-98b2-33ca72a987c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591051566","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591051566"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 30c3cffb-b148-424b-98b2-33ca72a987c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591052432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591052432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 30c3cffb-b148-424b-98b2-33ca72a987c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591052755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591052755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 30c3cffb-b148-424b-98b2-33ca72a987c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591054007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591054005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 30c3cffb-b148-424b-98b2-33ca72a987c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591057588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591057588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 30c3cffb-b148-424b-98b2-33ca72a987c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591058581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591058581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 30c3cffb-b148-424b-98b2-33ca72a987c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591058839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591058839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 30c3cffb-b148-424b-98b2-33ca72a987c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591059800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591059799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 30c3cffb-b148-424b-98b2-33ca72a987c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591062746","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591062746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 30c3cffb-b148-424b-98b2-33ca72a987c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591063789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591063789"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 30c3cffb-b148-424b-98b2-33ca72a987c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591064274","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591064274"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 30c3cffb-b148-424b-98b2-33ca72a987c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591068875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591068875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 30c3cffb-b148-424b-98b2-33ca72a987c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_19"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591068937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591068937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 30c3cffb-b148-424b-98b2-33ca72a987c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591090064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591090064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 9eb3ad22-5f4a-4a5b-8720-dc51b12c69dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_i_y"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591096759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591096759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 9eb3ad22-5f4a-4a5b-8720-dc51b12c69dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_v_a_f"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591103404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591103404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 9eb3ad22-5f4a-4a5b-8720-dc51b12c69dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_u_z"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591110925","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591110924"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 9eb3ad22-5f4a-4a5b-8720-dc51b12c69dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_u_z"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591117605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591117605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 9eb3ad22-5f4a-4a5b-8720-dc51b12c69dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_f_u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591124277","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591124277"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 9eb3ad22-5f4a-4a5b-8720-dc51b12c69dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_i_v"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591130959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591130959"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 9eb3ad22-5f4a-4a5b-8720-dc51b12c69dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_p_s"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591137631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591137631"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 9eb3ad22-5f4a-4a5b-8720-dc51b12c69dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_z_f"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591144247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591144247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 9eb3ad22-5f4a-4a5b-8720-dc51b12c69dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_g_f"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591151708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591151708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 9eb3ad22-5f4a-4a5b-8720-dc51b12c69dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_g_f"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591158301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591158301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 9eb3ad22-5f4a-4a5b-8720-dc51b12c69dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_f_n"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591164955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591164954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 9eb3ad22-5f4a-4a5b-8720-dc51b12c69dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_r_d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591172439","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591172439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 9eb3ad22-5f4a-4a5b-8720-dc51b12c69dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_r_d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591185610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591185609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 9eb3ad22-5f4a-4a5b-8720-dc51b12c69dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_f_r_d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591191127","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591191127"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 9eb3ad22-5f4a-4a5b-8720-dc51b12c69dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_f_r_d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591198461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591198461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 9eb3ad22-5f4a-4a5b-8720-dc51b12c69dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_f_r_d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591204732","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591204730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 9eb3ad22-5f4a-4a5b-8720-dc51b12c69dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_f_r_d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591214017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591214017"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591222700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591222700"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591244490","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591244489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591260436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591260436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591322329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591322329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591325527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591325527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591340334","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591340334"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591358837","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591358837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591363741","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591363740"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591368021","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591368021"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591371569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591371569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591375857","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591375857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591378676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591378676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591381772","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591381772"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591390361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591390361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591394451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591394451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591398789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591398788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591403170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591403170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591409900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591409900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591415193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591415193"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591418218","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591418218"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591420995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591420995"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591424735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591424735"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591430256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591430256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591433881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591433881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591451620","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591451620"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591457373","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591457372"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591463502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591463502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591470689","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591470688"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591476754","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591476754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 4b156de4-b22f-4176-8424-9a64a1601a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591486744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591486743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591490122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591490122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591494303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591494303"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591499651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591499651"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591505342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591505342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591521644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591521644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591526213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591526213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591530668","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591530668"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591533679","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591533679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591539494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591539493"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591545097","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591545097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591549348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591549347"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591553600","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591553600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591573239","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591573239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591577826","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591577826"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591581030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591581030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591584117","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591584117"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591587005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591587005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591591283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591591282"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591594609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591594609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591602240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591602240"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591605753","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591605753"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591609048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591609048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591612278","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591612278"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591615519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591615518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591619272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591619271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591623584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591623584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591626970","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591626970"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591630033","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591630033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591635792","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591635791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591641089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591641088"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591645426","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591645425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591649883","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591649883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591656044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591656041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..25.off2.18__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591661587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591661587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 263df881-c60f-4a0e-8b81-42334d273d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591669948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591669948"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 8a4f3e14-4939-4ad5-9cb0-f3393c1a4574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_t-k-g"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591673048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591673047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 8a4f3e14-4939-4ad5-9cb0-f3393c1a4574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_l-z-g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591674060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591674060"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 8a4f3e14-4939-4ad5-9cb0-f3393c1a4574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_g_l-z-g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591679151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591679151"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 8a4f3e14-4939-4ad5-9cb0-f3393c1a4574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_g_l-z-g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591690906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591690905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gunia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GUNIA"," userResponse":" GUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591694395","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591694395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gunia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GUNIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591695941","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591695941"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gauni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAUNI"," userResponse":" GAUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591699517","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591699517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gauni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591701080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591701080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" GOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591704265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591704265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591705819","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591705818"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" giza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591709257","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591709257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" giza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591710852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591710852"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591714069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591714069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591715642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591715642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591719166","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591719165"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591720725","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591720725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591724077","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591724077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591725631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591725631"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" GOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591729214","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591729214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591730787","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591730786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GODORO"," userResponse":" GODORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591734153","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591734153"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GODORO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591736164","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591736164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591736337","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591736337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GODORO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591741858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591741858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591750450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591750449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591756034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591756034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591762922","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591762921"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..25.off2.18__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591767832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591767832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591782607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591782607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591787535","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591787533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" a810e56f-9c28-4878-89cb-9abcd7326575"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591797888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591797888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591798270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591798270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591798761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591798760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591799113","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591799113"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591799527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591799526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591800010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591800010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591800243","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591800242"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591803432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591803432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591803465","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591803465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591804179","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591804179"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591804582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591804582"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591804877","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591804877"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591805091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591805090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591805285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591805285"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591805618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591805617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591805851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591805850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591809049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591809049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591809462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591809462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591811988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591811988"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591812196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591812196"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591812402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591812402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591816055","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591816054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591819797","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591819797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591820835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591820835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591823538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591823538"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591823931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591823931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591824432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591824432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591824783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591824783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591825195","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591825195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591825680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591825679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591825921","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591825916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591829065","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591829064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591829124","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591829124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591829859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591829857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591830261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591830261"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591830555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591830555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591830766","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591830766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591830972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591830972"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591831292","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591831292"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591831532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591831532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591834141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591834140"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591834299","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591834299"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548591842090","data":{"timestamp":" 1548591842089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150810"," gameId":" 2ff36eb4-48f4-4d09-8bf5-5f95ab36378b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}